yourself
[Music]
foreign
all right guys so day one and Dr where
we're gonna be giving away 21 laptops
with rocket21 we partnered up with them
we're going to be giving away laptops
and challenges along with that I'm going
to be talking about how to trade during
the holidays let's be honest during the
holidays markets are slow a lot of
Traders tend to fail around this time so
I'm going to be teaching you guys how to
properly trade and then there's this guy
named um Griffin Stefan or Graham stuff
whatever supposed to be a financial guy
so he did a review on the day in the
life of my video and we're going to be
getting uh my live reaction on it so
stay tuned we got the scavenger hunt
we're going to be giving away uh laptops
rocket21 challenges uh education and uh
this man
[Music]
we're here in Dr right now we're gonna
be giving away 21 challenges and at the
same time we're going to give away 21
laptops we hid little Christmas balls
around the whole entire park the first
people to find it are gonna get their
challenges and they're gonna be getting
their brand new laptops that we hit
across the park so let's start
[Music]
bro that did not go as planned at all
what the [__] bro
yes sir yes yes yes so many people bro
so a big shout out to the community or
within Dr they had me as a special host
here in this class where I talked a
little bit about my trading approach a
psychology and obviously this was in
Spanish so it was a super dope
experience hopped on a little podcast
here with the team but being part of
this huge community in Latin America
shows me that I genuinely love giving
back and being close with the community
and exactly what we did here in Dr which
not only do a meet and greet but just
get to another Community there's
something I want to do with countries
all around the world so make sure to
drop a comment on what country I should
use next
[Music]
one weekend
okay you can't swim
okay
[Music]
today I was super late shout out to
everybody there again for all their love
and all the support that we got from
there but let's get back to trade can I
train in the holidays how can I train in
Christmas art I'm gonna break it down in
this chart very simple make sure you pay
attention because I'm dropping gems I've
never dropped before so this right here
is essentially the calendar right we
understand that the market moves in four
quarters there's three quarters in each
month as we know and the mod and the
market moves with good volume slow
volume or ranging market so for me
always based off of my four years of
experience the first three months of the
year which is January February March are
the good volume markets after that it
kind of gets a little bit ranging again
to my experience smart gets a little bit
slow at the end of this slash it's slope
volume with is the months after that
after that we get back into a good
volume which is pretty much kind of uh
November October and September which are
are good volume months and then December
is a ranging month to to the holidays so
now let's say you still want to trade on
those months there is a risk approach
you should have so when you are in a
good volume again good volume one of
these checks I risk anywhere from 1.5 to
2.5 risk when you're in a slow Market
you should risk anywhere from one
percent to about 1.5 and then if you're
in a ranging Market you should risk 0.5
to 1 so if you're in a
ranging Market why are you even taking
big trades in the first place and if you
are taking trades take them with low
risk so you control your psychology you
make sure you stay on your A game so
when we come back into high volume
markets you got your Capital ready to go
to go crazy in this but let's say you
still want to take high risk trades in
the Raging markets just simply because
you want to feel involved whatever the
case which is already wrong
you can still yes can I still trade with
no body markets yes big yes you just
need to have a trading plan so my
trading plan consists of every single
one of these points and every single one
of these points has a percentage towards
your grade we notice the first
conference can be anywhere from 10 to 30
towards your grade everything else after
that can be a Max of ten percent and if
we were to add all of these things
together it would give us a total of a
hundred percent making the trade you
would take an A plus setup which has a
very high probability of going in your
favor versus not so let's say you were
to take a trade and it doesn't have
let's say this Confluence or this
Confluence or this one it's no longer
going to be a hundred percent trade now
it's going to be around a 70 trade
making it AC so now you have to
determine and ask yourself is it worth
for me to take it with a point five
percent 1.5 or 2.5 ideally what we teach
in swing trading lab instead of forget
is your ideal setup would be a B plus
which is 80 and up so I'm going to go
through the holidays make sure you take
all of this into consideration let's go
all right so we're about to get a live
reaction on this guy's um reaction video
in my video but I don't know how to say
his name Griffin Stefan so Graham
Staffing is his name so we're gonna
start yeah so we gotta watch this video
okay I love watching these videos at the
day in the life of millionaires and
multi-millionaires and deca millionaires
but you know what who has the best life
is none other than the Forex
millionaires the the the people who
trade currencies and I I still don't
know how they make money but with that
said have you you know is a financial
advisor financial advisor you should
know how we make money in course but we
gotta watch this video in here it
actually looks really interesting it's
titled A Day in the Life of a Miami 4X
millionaire Trader by FX FX Alex G FX
Alex G yes
of course they're supreme Supreme
Flex whoa okay we're missing Louis
Vuitton in a Lamborghini or a Ferrari we
need one of those so now he goes on uh
pointing out that I don't have a shirt
for like two minutes of the whole entire
video and he's kind of points it out
like 10 times it almost seems like he's
never seen anybody without a shirt and
Compares me to liver King which I find
pretty funny so make sure you guys go
check out his video because if it gets a
hundred thousand likes he will basically
get FX Alex G on the side of his head so
I think that'll be hilarious
um it was just a little weird because he
said some things that he doesn't know
how Forex Traders make money but he's uh
you know supposedly Financial God
financial advisor the finance guy so
it's a a bit weird to know exactly how
you know us day Traders make money so I
find it funny make sure you guys
subscribe to the channel at 75k we have
a huge giveaway coming to all of you
guys so make sure you hit that subscribe
button because stay tuned 100 stay tuned
to the weekend of the day and the life
of a Forex millionaire whatever I'm
gonna make it specifically for you you
see exactly how how a weekend in my life
looks like so appreciate you guys for
watching the video all the way to the
end make sure to like comment and
subscribe and I'll see you guys in the
next video we're going to be doing a
house tour on my brand new house
um I've probably been in here I'd say
like five six seven days so I'm still
kind of moving settling in so make sure
you guys stay tuned that it's going to
be the next video and I'll see you guys
there